how to turn a great idea into a software
product begin work work more work
smarter tested not working
focus try a new way your first win but
it's only a start follow the process
test again you need to be sure go ahead
experiment
oops that hurt but you don't stop no
rest today rely on your team stay the
course improve the architecture improve
the code and improve the design goal I
get user feedback missing tweak it ok
now you have a great product share your
success celebrate call your mom make
great things happen make a difference
this is how it's done the way we've
always done time after time push the
limits accept new challenges and never
ever stop for 25 years bringing your
brightest ideas to life Alex
[Music]